Barack  B-PERSON
Obama   I-PERSON
was     O
born    O
in      O
Hawaii  B-LOC
in      O
1961    B-DATE
.       O

Apple   B-ORG
released O
the     O
iPhone  B-PRODUCT
in      O
2007    B-DATE
.       O

Sundar  B-PERSON
Pichai  I-PERSON
became  O
CEO     O
of      O
Google  B-ORG
in      O
2015    B-DATE
.       O

The     O
Olympics B-EVENT
were    O
held    O
in      O
Tokyo   B-LOC
in      O
2021    B-DATE
.       O

Amazon  B-ORG
was     O
founded O
by      O
Jeff    B-PERSON
Bezos   I-PERSON
in      O
Seattle B-LOC
.       O

Tesla   B-ORG
unveiled O
the     O
Cybertruck B-PRODUCT
in      O
2019    B-DATE
.       O

Marie   B-PERSON
Curie   I-PERSON
won     O
the     O
Nobel   B-AWARD
Prize   I-AWARD
in      O
Physics B-FIELD
.       O

Microsoft B-ORG
headquarters O
are     O
in      O
Redmond B-LOC
,       O
Washington B-LOC
.       O

Lionel  B-PERSON
Messi   I-PERSON
joined  O
Inter   B-ORG
Miami   I-ORG
in      O
2023    B-DATE
.       O

Mount   B-LOC
Everest I-LOC
is      O
the     O
highest O
peak    O
in      O
the     O
world   O
.       O

Satya   B-PERSON
Nadella I-PERSON
became  O
CEO     O
of      O
Microsoft B-ORG
in      O
2014    B-DATE
.       O

The     O
Eiffel  B-LOC
Tower   I-LOC
is      O
in      O
Paris   B-LOC
.       O

Facebook B-ORG
changed  O
its      O
name     O
to       O
Meta     B-ORG
in       O
2021     B-DATE
.        O

Serena   B-PERSON
Williams I-PERSON
won      O
the      O
US       B-EVENT
Open     I-EVENT
in       O
2014     B-DATE
.        O

The      O
Amazon   B-LOC
River    I-LOC
flows    O
through  O
Brazil   B-LOC
.        O

J.K.     B-PERSON
Rowling  I-PERSON
wrote    O
Harry    B-WORK
Potter   I-WORK
in       O
1997     B-DATE
.        O

NASA     B-ORG
launched O
Apollo   B-PROJECT
11       I-PROJECT
in       O
1969     B-DATE
.        O

Cristiano B-PERSON
Ronaldo   I-PERSON
scored    O
his       O
800th     O
goal      O
in        O
2021      B-DATE
.         O

The       O
Taj       B-LOC
Mahal     I-LOC
is        O
located   O
in        O
Agra      B-LOC
.         O

Samsung   B-ORG
released  O
the       O
Galaxy    B-PRODUCT
S21       I-PRODUCT
in        O
2021      B-DATE
.         O

Greta     B-PERSON
Thunberg  I-PERSON
spoke     O
at        O
the       O
UN        B-ORG
in        O
2019      B-DATE
.         O

The       O
Amazon    B-ORG
Prime     I-ORG
Day       I-ORG
sale      O
started   O
in        O
2015      B-DATE
.         O

Roger     B-PERSON
Federer   I-PERSON
won       O
his       O
20th      O
Grand     B-EVENT
Slam      I-EVENT
title     O
in        O
2018      B-DATE
.         O

The       O
Sydney    B-LOC
Opera     I-LOC
House     I-LOC
opened    O
in        O
1973      B-DATE
.         O

Alibaba   B-ORG
was       O
founded   O
by        O
Jack      B-PERSON
Ma        I-PERSON
in        O
China     B-LOC
.         O

The       O
World     B-EVENT
Cup       I-EVENT
was       O
held      O
in        O
Russia    B-LOC
in        O
2018      B-DATE
.         O

Shakespeare B-PERSON
wrote      O
Romeo      B-WORK
and        I-WORK
Juliet     I-WORK
in         O
1597       B-DATE
.          O

The        O
Burj       B-LOC
Khalifa    I-LOC
opened     O
in         O
Dubai      B-LOC
in         O
2010       B-DATE
.          O

Taylor     B-PERSON
Swift      I-PERSON
released   O
the        O
album      O
1989       B-WORK
in         O
2014       B-DATE
.          O

